# Yarotskyi Yevhenii

# Front End Developer

### PERSONAL DATA

**Date of Birth:** 7<sup>th</sup> of April 1994 **Location:** Wroclaw, Poland **Mobile:** +48 733 682 044

**E-mail:** <u>evarotskiy94@gmail.com</u>

**Skype:** shargat94

**Viber/Telegram:** +48 733 682 044

**LinkedIn:** <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/yevyarotskyi/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/yevyarotskyi/</a>

## **OBJECTIVE**

**Desired Position:** Middle Front End Developer

I started learning Front End in 2014. Since that time got experience with **Digital Marketing (2 years)** and **ECommerce (1.5 years)** projects. During my career I worked with the projects of different sizes and teams, most often with Scrum methodology.

I have a solid knowledge of common FED languages and such frameworks as **VueJS** and **Angular**. I always follow trending FED technologies and ready to implement them in the projects I am working on.

In future I investigate the possibility to grow into **Full Stack Developer** and to achieve it I started learning **Java** and Back End technologies in free time.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, EcmaScript

Libraries: jQuery, Bootstrap

Frameworks: VueJS, AngularJS, Angular2

Preprocessors: LESS, SASS, SCSS

Task Runners: Gulp, Grunt, WebPack

**CMS:** Hybris, Wordpress **VCS:** Git, GitHub, BitBucket

External sevices and APIs: Google Maps, Google Streets, Google Geolocation, Google Analytics,

Google Tag Manager, Smarty Streets, Bazaarvoice, SalesForce, Hotjar

Workflow technologies: Jira, Confluence, Scrum

IDEs: Intellij IDEA, WebStorm, Sublime Text 3

Other technologies: BEM, Website Adaptivity and Cross-Browser Compatibility

### **EDUCATION**

2011 – 2017. Ukraine, Kiev, National Aviation University. Higher, Specialist. Speciality: "Electronic Devices and Systems"

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## GORILLA

## **Gorilla Group**

**Position:** Front End Developer

Website: <a href="https://www.gorillagroup.com/">https://www.gorillagroup.com/</a>

**Location:** Wroclaw, Poland

**Time:** October 2017 – Present

### **Responsibilities:**

Working with E-commerce projects: both delivery (projects from scratch) and managed service (supporting existing projects) departments.

Bug fixing and implementing new features.

Writing specifications for the projects and internal workflows of the company.

Preparing presentations and manuals about different topics of Front End for internal usage.

Communication and meetings with clients.

### **Technologies used:**

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, EcmaScript, jQuery, jQuery Validation, VueJS, Angular2, Git, Github, Bitbucket, LESS, SASS, SCSS, Grunt, WebPack, BEM, Hybris, Intellij IDEA, Jira, Confluence, Scrum



#### **Admixer**

Position: Front End Developer
Website: <a href="https://admixer.ua/">https://admixer.ua/</a>

**Location:** Kiev, Ukraine

Time: August 2015 – March 2017

## Responsibilities:

Creating markup for the websites from scratch using PSD/Sketch templates.

Fixing Javascript bugs for digital web banners.

Working and implementing different APIs and external libraries to websites and digital web banners.

## **Technologies used:**

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, AngularJS, Git, Github, LESS, Gulp, Worksection, Confluence

## **PORTFOLIO**

Mercedes Benz Canada		
Website:	https://www.mercedes-benz-shop.ca	
Localization:	Canada	
Project Industry:	B2C, E-commerce, parts and accessories for cars	
Position:	Front End Developer	
Overall Team Size:	1 FED, 5 BEDs, 1 QA, 2 Managers, 1 Project Manager, 1 Project Lead, 1 Delivery Lead	
Responsibilities:	Front-end development APIs: Google Tag Manager, Hotjar, BazaarVoice Bug fixing Communication with the client	
Tools & Technologies:	Platform: Hybris 6.4 Tools: Intellij IDEA, Confluence, Jira, BitBucket Languages & Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, jQuery Validation, VueJS, SASS, Grunt, BEM	

SPECIALIZEII Specialized		
Website:	https://www.specialized.com	
Localization:	USA, World	
Project Industry:	B2C, E-commerce, bikes and equipment for riders	
Position:	Front End Developer	
Overall Team Size:	3 FEDs, 8 BEDs, 2 QA, 2 Managers, 1 Project Manager	
Responsibilities:	Front-end development	

	Implementation of new features and APIs ie: SalesForce, Smarty Streets, Google Streets, Google Maps, Google Geolocation Bug fixing Communication with the client Cooperating with development team from client's side Creating functional specifications and documentation for internal usage
Tools & Technologies:	Platform: Hybris 6.3 Tools: Intellij IDEA, Confluence, Jira, BitBucket, Slack Languages & Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, jQuery Validation, VueJS, LESS, Grunt, BEM

AMERICAN BUILDING COMPONENTS National Construction Instruments		
Website:	https://shop.abcmetalroofing.com https://shop.mbci.com	
Localization:	USA	
Project Industry:	B2B, E-commerce, instruments and supplies for construction companies	
Position:	Front End Developer	
Overall Team Size:	3 FEDs, 7 BEDs, 2 QA, 1 Manager, 1 Project Manager, 1 Project Lead	
Responsibilities:	Front-end development Implementation of new features Bug fixing Communication with the client Creating functional specifications and documentation for internal usage	
Tools & Technologies:	Platform: Hybris 6.2 Tools: Intellij IDEA, Confluence, Jira, BitBucket Languages & Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, jQuery Validation, VueJS, LESS, Grunt	